<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blueprint Analytics</title>
    <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Blueprint Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Research Design</title>
      <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/01_design/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/01_design/</guid>
      <description>I will assist you in developing a blueprint for your research. I will advise you on defining a clear and answerable research question, and on the choice of study type, data collection methodologies, and statistical analyses for your research.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data analysis</title>
      <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/02_analysis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/02_analysis/</guid>
      <description>Working with you, I analyse your data from start to finish. I clean the data, generate graphical and numeric summaries, and undertake statistical inference testing. All analysis are presented in a comprehensive report that includes interpretations of the statistics and how to report the results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data presentation &amp; reporting</title>
      <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/03_data-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/03_data-presentation/</guid>
      <description>I have solutions for effectively presenting your data, whether you need a table or a choropleth map. I customise the style, format, and functionality of the my reports, and standalone plots and tables according to your needs. Do you need black-and-white versions for a print journal and full-colour versions for a presentation? Do you want a report with interactive or animated plots for your website? I have you covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open research workflows</title>
      <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/04_open-workflows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/04_open-workflows/</guid>
      <description>I specialise in developing workflows for reproducible research and open research using open-source software and platforms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Training</title>
      <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/05_training/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/services/05_training/</guid>
      <description>If you or people in your organisation need training, I create courses and content that suit your needs in the areas of research methods, interpreting data, reporting and presenting data, and training on the use the statistical programming language R.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/about/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a physiologist with over 20 years of experience in research design, analysis, and training in the biomedical sciences.
I also have more than a decade of experience in the pharmaceutical industry doing consultancy work, training, and conducting market research, so I am adept at planning and executing research and training programmes in a commercial environment.
For more information on the services I offer, continue to browse the information on this website or contact me to arrange a free consultation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apps</title>
      <link>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/apps/apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.blueprint-analytics.net/apps/apps/</guid>
      <description>I have developed two free online apps. One for basic statistical analysis (statR ), and one for basic plotting of data (plotR ).
Please feel free to make use of them.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
